The best thing about reading the PIKA program is that you get in a sports class.
I have grown a lot as a person by being able to become friends with and spend time with other elite athletes his has
Similar ambition and similar lifestyle like me.
Pika - professional sports career and working life, 180 credits
Pika - an education for you who are elite athletes - regardless of sports
Even though we are doing different sports, still very much similarities are
Especially the mental part is very similar in all sports,
And it is above all what we learn from each other.
My name is Tobias Tisell and plugged the Pika program at Halmstad University
With a focus on Golf here on the elite environment.
Today I have stopped playing golf and working as a project coordinator at
Corporate incubator high five in Halmstad.
The courses on the Pika program have helped me very much in my working life around that
put a structure in everyday life around my work, set goals
Be able to adapt very much to the rest of the environment in the workplace.
Generally speaking, the courses have helped to create strategies, think step ahead,
Which is very common as an athlete and sports woman.
My name is Alice Andersson and I am a road cyclist and read last year on the Pika program.
I started reading on the Pika program because I am an elite athlete
and I was looking for any employment that I could have in combination with my elite sports
Which was still fun and felt evolving.
So when I heard about the Pika program here in Halmstad, I was super tagged.
I did not know that you could read sports science at the university level
So when I heard about it, I felt it suited me perfectly.
There are not many places that exist here in Halmstad.
Then we also have access to the gym here at the university and it is fantastic that we get it
There is everything we need to be able to develop physically.
My name is Michaela Karlsson and I have studied a spike and I graduated this summer.
After my education, I got a position as a writer at the Swedish Table Tennis Association,
And also a very honorable role as the league captain for the youngest girls.
I learned a lot about not just ..
... psychology or nutrition without i learned a lot about myself as a person
And it has developed me and I am very grateful that I was studying at college,
And that I am there as I am today.